{
    "subject": "resource/James_Newton_Howard",
    "predicate": "property/placeOfBirth",
    "object": "Los Angeles",
    "human_readable": "James Newton Howard was born in Los Angeles.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8940057754516602,
            "question": "Where was James Newton Howard born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4923510253429413,
            "question": "What is James Newton Howard known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.40012994408607483,
            "question": "In what city did James Newton Howard's career begin?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.21821027994155884,
            "question": "What type of work is James Newton Howard known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.16750697791576385,
            "question": "Has James Newton Howard won any awards for his work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15785567462444305,
            "question": "Has James Newton Howard collaborated with any famous directors?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.15362583100795746,
            "question": "Is there anything unique about James Newton Howard's musical style?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1528855711221695,
            "question": "What is the name of James Newton Howard's most acclaimed work?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1421971470117569,
            "question": "Does James Newton Howard have a website or social media presence?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.13163568079471588,
            "question": "Are there any notable films that feature James Newton Howard's music?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=James Newton Howard was born in Los Angeles.",
            "html": "dbpedia_6925_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does James Newton Howard have a website or social media presence?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6925_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of James Newton Howard's most acclaimed work?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6925_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is there anything unique about James Newton Howard's musical style?",
            "html": "dbpedia_6925_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_102.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_112.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_119.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_128.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_30.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_61.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_66.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_6925_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"James Newton Howard was born in Los Angeles\" based on the provided context information:\n\n`{'output': 'no'}`\n\nThis answer because the documents mention different birthplaces for James Newton Howard, including Los Angeles (June 9, 1951) and June 1951 (without specifying the city), but another document explicitly states that he was born in \"June\" without providing a specific day of month."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe documents provide several details about James Newton Howard, including his birthplace, which is mentioned as Los Angeles, California. Therefore, the statement \"James Newton Howard was born in Los Angeles\" is supported by the given context information."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "All the sources confirm his birthplace as Los Angeles.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}